Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook UP150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Yearbook, 1924 -- 2020; UP150.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 80 Volumes; 5757 Digital Object(s)
  - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book [yearbook], UP150.001.030.00001 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 56, UP150.001.030.00001.00057 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 57, UP150.001.030.00001.00058 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 58, UP150.001.030.00001.00059 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 59, UP150.001.030.00001.00060 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 60, UP150.001.030.00001.00061 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 61, UP150.001.030.00001.00062 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 62, UP150.001.030.00001.00063 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 63, UP150.001.030.00001.00064 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 64, UP150.001.030.00001.00065 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 65, UP150.001.030.00001.00066 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 66, UP150.001.030.00001.00067 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 67, UP150.001.030.00001.00068 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 68, UP150.001.030.00001.00069 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 69, UP150.001.030.00001.00070 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 70, UP150.001.030.00001.00071 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 71, UP150.001.030.00001.00072 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 72, UP150.001.030.00001.00073 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 73, UP150.001.030.00001.00074 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 74, UP150.001.030.00001.00075 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 75, UP150.001.030.00001.00076 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 76, UP150.001.030.00001.00077 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 77, UP150.001.030.00001.00078 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 78, UP150.001.030.00001.00079 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 79, UP150.001.030.00001.00080 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 80, UP150.001.030.00001.00081 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 81, UP150.001.030.00001.00082 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 82, UP150.001.030.00001.00083 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 83, UP150.001.030.00001.00084 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 84, UP150.001.030.00001.00085 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 85, UP150.001.030.00001.00086 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 86, UP150.001.030.00001.00087 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 87, UP150.001.030.00001.00088 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 88, UP150.001.030.00001.00089 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 89, UP150.001.030.00001.00090 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 90, UP150.001.030.00001.00091 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 91, UP150.001.030.00001.00092 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 92, UP150.001.030.00001.00093 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 93, UP150.001.030.00001.00094 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 94, UP150.001.030.00001.00095 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 95, UP150.001.030.00001.00096 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 96, UP150.001.030.00001.00097 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 97, UP150.001.030.00001.00098 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 98, UP150.001.030.00001.00099 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 99, UP150.001.030.00001.00100 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 100, UP150.001.030.00001.00101 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 101, UP150.001.030.00001.00102 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 102, UP150.001.030.00001.00103 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 103, UP150.001.030.00001.00104 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 104, UP150.001.030.00001.00105 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 105, UP150.001.030.00001.00106 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 106, UP150.001.030.00001.00107 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 107, UP150.001.030.00001.00108 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 108, UP150.001.030.00001.00109 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 109, UP150.001.030.00001.00110 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 110, UP150.001.030.00001.00111 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 111, UP150.001.030.00001.00112 (Volume 30)
    - 1971 Tufts University School of Medicine Scut Book, page 112, UP150.001.030.00001.00113 (Volume 30)
    - Medical School yearbook, 1971, back cover, UP150.001.030.00001.00114 (Volume 30)
      From Medical School yearbook, 1971.
  - Tufts University School of Medicine [yearbook], 1972; UP150.001.031.00001 (Volume 31)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1972.
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, cover, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00001 (Volume 31)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1972.
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, inside cover, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00002 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, title page, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00003 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 1, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00004 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 2, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00005 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 3, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00006 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 4, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00007 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 5, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00008 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 6, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00009 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 7, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00010 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 8, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00011 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 9, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00012 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 10, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00013 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 11, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00014 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 12, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00015 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 13, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00016 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 14, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00017 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 15, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00018 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 16, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00019 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 17, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00020 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 18, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00021 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 19, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00022 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 20, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00023 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 21, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00024 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 22, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00025 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 23, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00026 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 24, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00027 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 25, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00028 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 26, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00029 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 27, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00030 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 28, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00031 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 29, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00032 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 30, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00033 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 31, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00034 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 32, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00035 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 33, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00036 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 34, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00037 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 35, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00038 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 36, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00039 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 37, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00040 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 38, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00041 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 39, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00042 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 40, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00043 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 41, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00044 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 42, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00045 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 43, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00046 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 44, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00047 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 45, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00048 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 46, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00049 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 47, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00050 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 48, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00051 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 49, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00052 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 50, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00053 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 51, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00054 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 52, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00055 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 53, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00056 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 54, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00057 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 55, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00058 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 56, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00059 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 57, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00060 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 58, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00061 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 59, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00062 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 60, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00063 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 61, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00064 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 62, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00065 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 63, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00066 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 64, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00067 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 65, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00068 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 66, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00069 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 67, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00070 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 68, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00071 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 69, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00072 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 70, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00073 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 71, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00074 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 72, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00075 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 73, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00076 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 74, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00077 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 75, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00078 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 76, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00079 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 77, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00080 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 78, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00081 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 79, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00082 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 80, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00083 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 81, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00084 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 82, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00085 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 83, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00086 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 84, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00087 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 85, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00088 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 86, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00089 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 87, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00090 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 88, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00091 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 89, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00092 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 90, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00093 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 91, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00094 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 92, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00095 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 93, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00096 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 94, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00097 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 95, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00098 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 96, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00099 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 97, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00100 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 98, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00101 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 99, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00102 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 100, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00103 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 101, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00104 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 102, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00105 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 103, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00106 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 104, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00107 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 105, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00108 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 106, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00109 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 107, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00110 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 108, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00111 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 109, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00112 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 110, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00113 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 111, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00114 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 112, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00115 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 113, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00116 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 114, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00117 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 115, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00118 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 116, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00119 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 117, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00120 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 118, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00121 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 119, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00122 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 120, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00123 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 121, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00124 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 122, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00125 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 123, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00126 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 124, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00127 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 125, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00128 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 126, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00129 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 127, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00130 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 128, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00131 (Volume 31)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, back cover, 1972; UP150.001.031.00001.00132 (Volume 31)
  - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine [yearbook], UP150.001.032.00001 (Box 32)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1973.
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, front cover, UP150.001.032.00001.00001 (Box 32)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1973.
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 1, UP150.001.032.00001.00002 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 2, UP150.001.032.00001.00003 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 3, UP150.001.032.00001.00004 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 4, UP150.001.032.00001.00005 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 5, UP150.001.032.00001.00006 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 6, UP150.001.032.00001.00007 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 7, UP150.001.032.00001.00008 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 8, UP150.001.032.00001.00009 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 9, UP150.001.032.00001.00010 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 10, UP150.001.032.00001.00011 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 11, UP150.001.032.00001.00012 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 12, UP150.001.032.00001.00013 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 13, UP150.001.032.00001.00014 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 14, UP150.001.032.00001.00015 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 15, UP150.001.032.00001.00016 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 16, UP150.001.032.00001.00017 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 17, UP150.001.032.00001.00018 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 18, UP150.001.032.00001.00019 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 19, UP150.001.032.00001.00020 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 20, UP150.001.032.00001.00021 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 21, UP150.001.032.00001.00022 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 22, UP150.001.032.00001.00023 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 23, UP150.001.032.00001.00024 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 24, UP150.001.032.00001.00025 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 25, UP150.001.032.00001.00026 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 26, UP150.001.032.00001.00027 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 27, UP150.001.032.00001.00028 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 28, UP150.001.032.00001.00029 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 29, UP150.001.032.00001.00030 (Box 32)
    - 1973 Tufts University School of Medicine, back cover, UP150.001.032.00001.00031 (Box 32)
  - TUSM '74 [yearbook], 1974; UP150.001.033.00001 (Volume 33)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1974.
    - TUSM 74, front cover, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00001 (Volume 33)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1974
    - TUSM 74, inside cover (1), 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00002 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, inside cover (2), 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00003 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 1, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00004 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 2, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00005 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 3, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00006 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 4, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00007 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 5, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00008 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 6, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00009 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 7, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00010 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 8, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00011 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 9, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00012 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 10, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00013 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 11, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00014 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 12, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00015 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 13, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00016 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 14, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00017 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 15, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00018 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 16, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00019 (Volume 33)
    - TUSM 74, page 17, 1974; UP150.001.033.00001.00020 (Volume 33)